rockdizmusic.com 2014-06-28

# Privacy Policy

The RPO Productions, LLC (Rockdizmusic) Privacy Policy, in conjunction with the Terms of Service and other terms and conditions of use which are incorporated herein by reference and may be posted and applicable to specific services, governs your use of the Rockdizmusic website (Rockdizmusic.com”) and are referred to as the “Agreement” throughout.  
Rockdizmusic may modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your use of the website and any related services (“Services”) indicates your acceptance of the Agreement.  
Any Content uploaded by you to Rockdizmusic becomes published Content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.  
Rockdizmusic is committed to protecting your privacy online. We will not rent, sell or share your personal information with third parties, except when required by law.

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

When you visit Rockdizmusic you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse Rockdizmusic.

  1. **Personal Information You Choose to Provide**  
_Credit Card Information_  
If you choose to purchase products or services from us or our partners, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:  
Name  
Mailing address  
E-mail address  
Credit card number  
Home and business phone number  
E-mail Information  
In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. 
  2. **Web Site Use Information**  
Similar to other Web sites, Rockdizmusic utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?“) and Web server logs to collect information about how Rockdizmusic is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Rockdizmusic, and the Web sites visited just before and just after Rockdizmusic. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual. 

## HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to Rockdizmusic, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers’ personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers.

## WHAT ARE COOKIES?

Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

## HOW DO WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM COOKIES?

We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about Rockdizmusic users’ browsing activities in order to constantly improve Rockdizmusic and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve Rockdizmusic to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers.  
Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to Rockdizmusic as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit Rockdizmusic and evaluate Rockdizmusic’s visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual e-mail address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.  
We also allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit Rockdizmusic. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

## SHARING INFORMATION WITH AFFILIATES

From time to time you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on Rockdizmusic. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies.

## SHARING INFORMATION WITH STRATEGIC PARTNERS

We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and e-mail for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information, and we will not share information regarding your social security number or other personal financial data that we may have.

## NOTICE OF NEW SERVICES AND CHANGES

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to Rockdizmusic, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our client, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on a response box when you receive such an offer, updating your mailing preferences in your account, or by sending us an e-mail request from our contact page.

##  DO WE SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS?

When you send confidential personal credit card information to our processors like PayPal and Google, from Rockdizmusic, a secure server software which they have licensed encrypts all information you input before it is sent to them. The information is scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches their Web site.  
Other e-mail that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an unsecured e-mail.

## HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

Information Security.  
We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.  
Evaluation of Information Protection Practices.  
Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information.  
Employee Access, Training and Expectations.  
Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.

## DO WE DISCLOSE INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

## WHAT ABOUT LEGALLY COMPELLED DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION?

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

## WHAT ABOUT OTHER WEB SITES LINKED TO Rockdizmusic?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from Rockdizmusic nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of Rockdizmusic.  
Please remember that when you use a link to go from Rockdizmusic to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link to Rockdizmusic, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

## YOUR CONSENT

By using Rockdizmusic you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on Rockdizmusic to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
